[
    {
        "numb": 1,
        "question": " STD stands for ____________",
        "answer": "Software Test Documents",
        "options": [
            "Software Test Documents",
            "System Test Documents",
            "Software Traced Documents",
            "System Traced Documents"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 2,
        "question": "The SRS describes what the system should do with words and figures.",
        "answer": "True",
        "options": [
            "True",
			"False"
            
            
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 3,
        "question": "_______ is part of user documentation.",
        "answer": "Installation guide",
        "options": [
            "Code comment",
            "Parallel run",
            "Installation guide",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 4,
        "question": "The process of maintaining a record of project development and maintenance.",
        "answer": "Process documentation",
        "options": [
            "System documentation",
            "User documentation",
            "Product documentation",
            "Process documentation"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 5,
        "question": "This describes the objectives of a product and set out the constraints.",
        "answer": "SDP",
        "options": [
            "SDS",
            "SDP",
            "SDD",
            "DFS"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 6,
        "question": "____________ provide the detailed, specific application being developed.",
        "answer": "Appendices",
        "options": [
            "System models",
            "Appendices",
            "Index",
            "None of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 7,
        "question": "Which of the following should describe the technical terms used in the document?",
        "answer": "glossary)",
        "options": [
            "system architecture",
            "user requirements",
            "index",
            "glossary"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 8,
        "question": "The services provided for the user are described in which section?",
        "answer": "User requirements",
        "options": [
            "Collaboration",
            "Appendices",
			"User requirements",
			"None of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 9,
        "question": " ______________ architecture provides a high-level overview of the anticipated system architecture.",
        "answer": "Size indicator mnemonic",
        "options": [
            "System",
            "User",
            "Test",
            "Delimiter"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 10,
        "question": "How many diagrams are here in Unified Modelling Language?",
        "answer": "nine",
        "options": [
            "eight",
            "nine",
            "seven",
            "six"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 11,
        "question": "Which of the following does not relate to Evolutionary Process Model?",
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "options": [
            "Incremental Model",
            "Concurrent Development Model",
            "WINWIN Spiral Model",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 12,
        "question": "who consider diagrams as a type of Class diagram, component diagram, object diagram, and deployment diagram?",
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "options": [
            "structural",
            "behavioral",
            "non-behavioral",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 13,
        "question": "What is the major drawback of the Spiral Model?",
        "answer": "Doesn't work well for smaller projects",
        "options": [
            "Higher amount of risk analysis",
            "Strong approval and documentation control",
            "Additional functionalities are added later on",
            "Doesn't work well for smaller projects"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 14,
        "question": ".__________ represented by In UML diagrams, relationship between component parts and object.",
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "options": [
            "Requirements",
            "Development team & users",
            "Project type & associated risk",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 15,
        "question": "Model selection is based on _",
        "answer": "The address for the next instruction",
        "options": [
            "The accumulated memory location",
            "The instruction for the next instruction",
            "The data for the next instruction",
            "The address for the next instruction"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 16,
        "question": "which type they considered Activity diagram, use case diagram, collaboration diagram, and sequence diagram?",
        "answer": "behavioral",
        "options": [
            "structural",
            "non-structural",
            "non-behavioral",
            "behavioral"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 17,
        "question": "Which of the following models doesn't necessitate defining requirements at the earliest in the lifecycle?",
        "answer": "Spiral & Prototyping",
        "options": [
            "Compression",
            "Prototyping & Waterfall",
            "Spiral & RAD",
            "Spiral & Prototyping"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 18,
        "question": "simple name in UML Class and objects consist of __________.",
        "answer": "All of the mentioned",
        "options": [
            "Letters",
			"Digits",
			"Punctuation Characters",
            "All of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 19,
        "question": "which of these abstractions class consist?",
        "answer": "All of the mentioned",
        "options": [
            "Attributes",
            "Operations",
            "Set of the objects",
            "All of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 20,
        "question": "which of the following attribute is a data item held by?",
        "answer": "All of the mentioned",
        "options": [
            "Class",
            "Object",
            "All of the mentioned",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    }
]
    